Hero!
Take me with you!
Move this thing! Now!
I am never traveling with you again!
Aw, don't be like that.
You're making me sad.
We haven't even reached the mine yet.
Then stop making trouble every
single day, you worthless hero!
Beautiful.
It suits you well.
I think this is what you
should wear on the big day.
I think what I usually wear
would be just fine, though...
That won't do.
Your attire must befit
the Aquaraine family.
Isn't this a bit too extravagant?
You dislike it?
Pardon me. There's a visitor for milady.
Thank you for waiting.
Sorry to come without warning.
I wanted to ask you something
about healing magic...
Wait, why are you dressed like that?
It looks weird, doesn't it?
Of course not! You look super pretty.
I was just surprised because I so
rarely see you dressed like a noble.
I have an arranged marriage meeting.
Ah, I see.
Wait, what?!
Are you serious?! I mean,
are you... sure about this?
I'm only meeting him once
per His Majesty's orders.
I don't intend to marry him.
I'm still training, after all.
Training? How studious can you be?
So when are you meeting the guy?
In three days.
Who is he?
He's someone you know.
A member of the hero's party
of the Duchy of Luminaria.
I am honored to have
this audience with you.
My name is Soleil Graceheart.
Miss Cecilia.
It's good to see you again.
I believe the last time we met
was at the party celebrating
the defeat of the Demon King.
Yes, I believe so.
King Dartz told me
that you aren't interested in marriage
and have turned down
all proposals thus far.
I'm still training, after all.
These are fine tea leaves.
Huh?
And it's because you
defeated the Demon King
that we can enjoy such delicious tea now.
It wasn't me. It was all the hero.
But I'm sure he'd say it was
all of us who made it possible.
True.
And that's probably why he was
able to become a true hero.
That said...
there are some heroes
who are chosen to challenge the Demon
King solely for their strength.
You know about Miller, the hero
of the Gallis Empire, yes?
Yes.
This is only a rumor,
but I hear he's imprisoned
in the empire now.
That's a shame.
So why does each nation
have its own hero's party?
I'm sure you... no, anyone who's
a noble must have an inkling.
Because even as humanity was
being wiped out by demons,
the kings of each nation competed
for supremacy in the aftermath.
Why can't people just work hand in hand?
I feel the same way.
But thankfully, King Dartz is a wise man.
He is quite concerned about the signs
of conflict in our neighbor nations.
That must be why he accepted my proposal.
What do you mean?
Our marriage will make
it known far and wide
that the Duchy of Luminaria and the
Kingdom of Clariness are friends.
It will keep any countries with
malicious intentions in check.
Miss Cecilia...
Please do me the honor of marrying me.
And then,
let us guide this world
toward peace together.
Check this out.
Are you kidding me?
This is...
We ran into a monster nest
while we were mining.
They're so cute.
So cute.
It's a real problem.
I can't risk using my pickaxe now.
Which is why I asked an
official to contact the hero.
Could you please do something
about this without hurting them?
Got it! Leave this to us!
What do you think we should do, Yoki?
Why are you asking me?
You're the one who accepted the
quest with total confidence.
Yep!
You always give me good advice,
so I figured you'd have a
good idea this time, too!
Dude.
You seriously have no ideas at all?!
I'm sorry. This is all
far too much for me.
It would seem you don't understand
the significance of your own standing.
I made some big talk, but I
am still inexperienced myself.
I'm still training.
Let's put the marriage discussion
aside for the moment.
The truth is, I've been staying
in Minerva for some time now.
I'm in the midst of learning about
this country and its people.
And... why is that?
Nobles such as you and I need to have
an understanding of other countries.
If more nations understood each
other, more wars could be avoided.
So I ask this favor of you...
Any time that is convenient
for you will do.
Would you please...
teach me more about this country?
All right.
Thank you!
I can see that you have
very good intentions.
If it will lead us to friendlier
relations with the Duchy of Luminaria,
I would be happy to help.
Can I ask for your advice?
Sure, I guess.
It's about Cecilia's arranged marriage...
Huh?
What did you just say?!
Wait, you didn't know about it?
I was so shocked that I went to see her...
Cecilia! You can't go through with
an arranged marriage! Tell them no!
The king ordered me to.
You just can't! Tell them
you won't do it, Cecilia!
Yuga, if you're going to throw a
tantrum, do it in front of the king.
I don't want her to have
an arranged marriage.
And it's with Soleil, no less.
Soleil?
He's in the hero's party
of the Duchy of Luminaria.
He's about as good with
the sword as Raven.
He's the heir to an influential lord,
he's smart, he has impeccable manners...
Sorry. You'll have to try to
finish the quest on your own.
Huh?
Yoki?
Why... didn't she tell me?
Why?!
Can we help you, miss?
Um... I-Is Yuga...
Mikana!
I'm so glad you're here!
I was really stuck! I
can't handle this alone!
Alone? Where's the civilian?
Yoki just up and went back home.
Why?
We were talking about Cecilia's
arranged marriage and—
Yuga! You knew about that?
Oh, good! You knew about it, too!
What does he think he's going to do?
This is the orphanage.
Holy Mother!
I baked cookies for all of you today.
Here they are.
Yay! Cookies!
Guys, you have to say thank
you to the Holy Mother!
Thank you, Holy Mother!
Make sure you share them, okay?
Okay!
Holy Mother! Tell us a story!
Aw, I'd rather draw pictures!
Easy, now. Remember to take turns.
Let's eat the cookies first.
Who are you, mister?
I am the Holy Mother's helper.
Soleil!
It's true. I only hope
there's some way I can help.
Raise me up high!
Up... high?
What does that mean?
You don't know?
But you're a grown-up.
That's weird!
Soleil, pick her up with both hands.
Pardon me, then.
Now lift her up high.
L-Like this?
Wow! I'm way up high!
Lucky!
Me next!
Then me!
Come on, please!
I'm sorry, Soleil.
Don't tire yourself out, but could you
please do the same for the others?
All right.
Let's take turns, then, shall we?
Yay!
Soleil, thank you for your help.
The children were delighted.
Not at all. I should thank you
for the valuable experience.
I had no idea children played that way.
They don't in the Duchy of Luminaria?
I'm not sure.
As the heir to the Graceheart family,
I spent my childhood studying
and training with the sword.
I still study under my father every day.
I never have opportunities
to interact with our people.
So when I was chosen for the hero's party
and set out to slay the Demon King,
every little thing surprised me.
The other members laughed so loudly,
they'd get angry, and they were so honest.
Interacting with them directly made
me want to protect them all the more.
From the Demon King and from
any struggles they may face.
Protect them?
Is that presumptuous of me?
No, that's how I've always
tried to be, as well.
And...
I have asked someone with
great power for help at times.
Now, though, he helps people in
need without even being asked.
He sounds wonderful.
Yes.
I want to become worthy
of standing by his side.
I have a role model, as well.
You do?
Yes.
Then I guess we both still
have a long way to go!
Very true.
Thank you for today,
and I hope you'll teach me more tomorrow
about this country and its people.
I'm happy to do anything I can.
Thank you.
Well, then, see you tomorrow.
What in the world am I doing?!
I just... couldn't turn him down...
I'm working hard as an adventurer
now, and once I make a decent living,
I'm planning to ask her again, so...
Yoki seems to be having a lot of fun
now that he's made so many friends.
He's not the same Yoki who couldn't
leave the Demon King's castle.
I'm sure... he doesn't
feel the same about...
I'll make myself invisible
and go straight to her!
Vanish Wave!
Blue fire?
Yah!
I wasn't expecting to run
into a demon on my patrol.
Were you trying to hunt humans
down under cover of night?
Who are you?!
I am...
the Beast of Blue Fire!
BEAST OF BLUE FIRE
The Beast of... Blue Fire?
I incinerate evil with
the flames of justice!
I don't have time for you right now!
Why bother showing up here now, demon?!
What am I even gonna do when I see her?
You will not escape!
He erased it?!
What's going on?!
You're the guy on the wanted posters!
Hey, isn't that a demon?
There's a demon!
What's it doing here?!
That's right! Don't let that
demon take one step into Minerva!
Get lost!
Damn demon!
What'd you come here for?!
C-Come in.
Pardon me.
Milady, my husband showed me this.
Why did I have to reincarnate as a demon?
This is one of Kramen's...
Huh?!
This is... Yoki?
The Magic Swordsman of Black
Lightning... on a wanted poster?!
A demon attempted to infiltrate
Minerva last night.
Thankfully, we fought it off,
but we will increase
patrols and remain alert.
Stay focused, all of you!
And that concludes our captain's speech.
Yes, sir!
Opening the gate!
Shouldn't we check each
of them individually?
The demon that showed
up had horns and wings.
Anyone who doesn't appear
obviously suspicious is fine.
That's...
Yoki?!
Cecilia?!
Miss Cecilia.
Soleil?
Am I imagining it, or is he...
Um... it's all right!
I know him!
How did you get hurt?!
Hold still, please!
Okay...
What happened?
Are you finished healing
him, Miss Cecilia?
You said that you know him.
Oh... I'm sorry. Yoki is...
Just a guy she knows in passing.
I'm an adventurer she's helped out a lot.
Cecilia is kind to everyone, after all.
She even helps a guy like me.
I see.
I haven't introduced myself.
I am Soleil Graceheart.
I am hoping to become
Miss Cecilia's fiancé.
Yoki, um... I didn't tell
you about this, but...
Sorry for getting in the way
of your marriage meeting.
Well, have a good day.
We've had a bit of an incident.
I'll need you to cooperate.
Huh?
Irene, stay on watch over here.
Y-Yes, sir!
Look, I'm at my height
of seriousness here.
Translation: Rebecca Cottrill
Timing: Andy Ellis
Editing: Ashley Barboza
Quality Control: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka